<resources>
    <!--    labels resource-->
    <string name="app_name">exer2_sibor_b4l</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="retry">RETRY</string>
    <string name="app_header"><b><i>Which Disney Princess are you?</i></b></string>
    <string name="scroll_view">Find out which Disney Princess are you!</string>
    <string name="start_header"><i>You are:</i></string>

    <!--    character names resource-->
    <string name="disney_princesses">Disney Princesses</string>
    <string name="ariel_name">Ariel</string>
    <string name="aurora_name">Aurora</string>
    <string name="belle_name">Belle</string>
    <string name="cinderella_name">Cinderella</string>
    <string name="elsa_name">Elsa</string>
    <string name="jasmine_name">Jasmine</string>
    <string name="merida_name">Merida</string>
    <string name="mulan_name">Mulan</string>
    <string name="pocahontas_name">Pocahontas</string>
    <string name="rapunzel_name">Rapunzel</string>
    <string name="snow_white_name">Snow White</string>


    <!--    descriptions resource (per character)-->
    <!--    descriptions were taken from "https://disney.fandom.com/wiki/The_Disney_Wiki"-->

    <string name="ariel_char">
        Ariel is a bright, spirited, and headstrong mermaid princess with a strong passion for
        adventure and exploration. Despite this, Ariel\'s selflessness, compassion and intuitive
        way of thinking often resolve such problems, as she always takes full responsibility for
        her actions.
    </string>

    <string name="aurora_char">
        Aurora is a kind, elegant, graceful, angelic, and gentle person as well as a hopelessly
        romantic one. Despite her innocence and apparent dependence on others\' actions and
        opinions, Aurora isn\'t as passive or helpless as she may seem at first sight.
    </string>

    <string name="belle_char">
        Belle has gained a significant amount of intelligence over the years due to her love
        of books, which have provided her with an elevated vocabulary, an active imagination, and
        an open mind. Despite all this, she doesn\'t have very many friends.
    </string>

    <string name="cinderella_char">
        Cinderella declared herself independent and strong-willed by remaining kind-hearted and
        self-loving. She makes the most of her misfortunes by remaining optimistic of the
        possibilities of a brighter future.
    </string>

    <string name="elsa_char">
        Elsa appears calm, reserved, regal, graceful and poised. Beneath this cool and collected
        appearance, however, Elsa is quite turbulent. Elsa also has an altruistic disposition that
        contributes to her compassion towards her people.
    </string>

    <string name="jasmine_char">
        Jasmine is introduced as feisty and no-nonsense, with zero tolerance for anyone that
        belittles her. Strong-willed and defiant, Jasmine is not afraid to speak her mind, nor will
        she hesitate to stand up for what she believes is right.
    </string>

    <string name="merida_char">
        Merida is a very bold, brave, daring, courageous, stubborn, rebellious, and headstrong girl
        who does not fit the stereotypical princess role. She is very athletic, tends to be
        ungraceful, has bad manners, and is extremely tomboyish.
    </string>

    <string name="mulan_char">
        Mulan is a courageous, independent and an unselfish hero. She has a different level of
        determination and known to be a quick thinker that sometimes makes her impulsive.
    </string>

    <string name="pocahontas_char">
        Pocahontas is displayed as a noble, free-spirited, and highly spiritual young woman. She
        expresses wisdom beyond her years and offers kindness and guidance to those around her. She
        loves her homeland, adventure, and nature.
    </string>

    <string name="rapunzel_char">
        Rapunzel is a spirited and determined young woman. Additional misfortunes born through
        Rapunzel\'s upbringing would include such traits as anxiety and low self-esteem. Despite
        being fearful, she pushes herself forward to pursue her ambitions.
    </string>

    <string name="snow_white_char">
         Snow White is well known for her kindness and optimism - both of which act as her greatest
        strengths, as they\'ve guided her safely through the various hardships faced throughout her
        life. She is quick to charm. She can also be playful, and somewhat sassy.
    </string>

</resources>
